{
    "1": {
      "chinese": "讓我們直接切入正題吧，克萊爾，請做會議紀錄。",
      "question": "Let’s get down to business. Claire, _____  _____  ________, please.",
      "ans": "take the minutes"
    },
    "2": {
      "chinese": "這是腦力激盪會議;想到甚麼就說出來!誰有什麼點子了嗎?",
      "question": "This is a _____________ session; anything goes! Who’s got an idea.",
      "ans": "brainstorming"
    },
    "3": {
      "chinese": "我們為忠實顧客舉辦一場感恩派對如何?",
      "question": "How about throwing an ___________ party for our loyal customers.",
      "ans": "appreciation"
    },
    "4": {
      "chinese": "你的聲音聽起來失真了/怪怪的。你可以調整你那邊的音量嗎?",
      "question": "Your voice sounds distorted/weird. Could you adjust the ___________ on your side?",
      "ans": "volume"
    },
    "5": {
      "chinese": "連線不是很好。我們掛斷後再試一次吧。",
      "question": "The __________ isn’t great. Let’s hang up and try again.",
      "ans": "connection"
    },
    "6": {
      "chinese": "這場簡報的目的是要檢視去年的銷售數據。",
      "question": "The purpose of this presentation is to review last year’s sales__________.",
      "ans": "figures"
    },
    "7": {
      "chinese": "現在，我們就接著討論未來兩年所擬議的預算吧。",
      "question": "Now let’s move on to the proposed _________ for the next two years.",
      "ans": "budget"
    },
    "8": {
      "chinese": "這張圖表指出我們的產品在國內哪些地區最暢銷。",
      "question": "The ___________ here points out the regions of the country where our products have been selling the best.",
      "ans": "diagram"
    },
    "9": {
      "chinese": "有問題或意見請隨時打斷我。",
      "question": "Feel free to ____________ me at any time whit questions or comments.",
      "ans": "interrupt"
    },
    "10": {
      "chinese": "我想見個面能釐清所有的事情。",
      "question": "I think a ________________ would clear everything up.",
      "ans": "face-to-face"
    },
    "11": {
      "chinese": "當然可以。而且你來這裡的時候可以參觀工廠。",
      "question": "Sure. And you can _______ the plant when you’re here.",
      "ans": "tour"
    },
    "12": {
      "chinese": "我們設施的視察明天照原定計畫進行嗎?",
      "question": "Is tomorrow still on for the inspection of our_____________.",
      "ans": "facilities"
    },
    "13": {
      "chinese": "一切都安排的很完美。",
      "question": "Everything has been _____________ perfectly.",
      "ans": "arranged"
    },
    "14": {
      "chinese": "如果有的話，我偏好逃生門那排的座位。",
      "question": "If prefer an ______  ______ if one is available.",
      "ans": "exit row"
    },
    "15": {
      "chinese": "抱歉，逃生門那排的位子已被劃位。",
      "question": "I’m afraid the exit row seats have already been _____________.",
      "ans": "assigned"
    },
    "16": {
      "chinese": "您此行來訪的目的為何?",
      "question": "What is the __________ of your visit?",
      "ans": "purpose"
    },
    "17": {
      "chinese": "您有攜帶任何商業製品來本國嗎?",
      "question": "Are you bringing any ______________ items into the country?",
      "ans": "commercial"
    },
    "18": {
      "chinese": "只有一些商展要用的樣品。",
      "question": "Only some samples for a ________  ________.",
      "ans": "trade expo"
    },
    "19": {
      "chinese": "麻煩告訴我們要在哪裡設攤。",
      "question": "Would you show us where we’ll be __________  _____?",
      "ans": "setting up"
    },
    "20": {
      "chinese": "好的。我們可以在哪裡卸下我們的設備?",
      "question": "OK. And where can we ________ our equipment?",
      "ans": "unload"
    },
    "21": {
      "chinese": "你們在C103攤位。那是入口B的右邊。",
      "question": "You’re at _________  C103. That’s on the right side of entrance B.",
      "ans": "booth"
    },
    "22": {
      "chinese": "你們的產品和其他產品有什麼不同?",
      "question": "What makes your product different from ______  ________?",
      "ans": "the rest"
    },
    "23": {
      "chinese": "創新功能和優良服務的結合使我們與眾不同。",
      "question": "A combination of ______________ features and superior service sets us apart.",
      "ans": "innovative"
    },
    "24": {
      "chinese": "如果有什麼我能為您效勞，請隨時來電。",
      "question": "If there’s anything I can do for you, please don’t ___________ to call.",
      "ans": "hesitate"
    },
    "25": {
      "chinese": "好的。你一有追蹤查詢碼就通知我。",
      "question": "OK. Just let me know when you have the ____________  ____________ for the shipment.",
      "ans": "tracking number"
    }
  }
  